compusystems.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Statement | CompuSystems

CompuSystems is committed to building user trust and confidence by promoting and complying with business practices that help protect the privacy of those who visit our corporate websites, register online for the events we service, use our mobile apps, purchase our products online, and engage us to provide registration services (i.e., rely on us collect, store and disseminate their registration data). 

## 

### **CORPORATE WEBSITE VISITORS**

When you visit our website, we may automatically collect statistics about your visit. This information does not identify you personally, but rather about your visit to our website. We may monitor statistics such as how many people visit our site, which pages people visit, from which domains our visitors come and which browsers people use. We use these statistics about your visit for aggregation purposes only. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our website.

Personal information is requested when you order a product or service. For example, this information may include your company name, contact name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information and order details.  

_How We Use The Information We Collect From Corporate Website Visitors:_

We use personal information collected for a variety of purposes. In particular, we may collect your name, physical address, email address, and/or phone number to: 

  * conduct market research
  * fulfill the requests you initiate
  * allow you to participate in surveys, access and download materials, and use other interactive features on our services
  * fulfill other business purposes, such as e-mail marketing campaigns, data analysis, identifying usage trends
  * carry out functions we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (e) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (f) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain

CompuSystems processes data on behalf of event organizers. Specifically, CompuSystems collects and processes event registrant information and provides lead retrieval services to trade show exhibitors. CompuSystems does not share registrant data without event organizer permission. However, we reserve the right to share registrant information when required by subpoena, court order, applicable law, governmental statute, regulation or other legal process. Additionally, we may share this information when we have a good faith belief that the disclosure is necessary to prevent or respond to fraud, defend our websites, mobile applications or other services against attacks, or protect our property and security, or our customers and users.

The following is our privacy policy as it pertains to these two customer segments:

**Meeting, Convention & Trade Show Registrants**

We have taken a number of steps to assure the protection of personal or confidential information sent to or from us.

First, as it pertains to online transactions, we require that a secure session be established. This is done any time registrants supply or access personal or confidential information in one of our online areas. This technology creates a private conversation that only the communicating computers understand, ensuring that the transmitted information remains confidential. Specifically, when registrants access pages requesting or presenting financial or personal data, we utilize 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to prevent others from accessing it while in transit. Most browsers display a padlock icon in the bottom right-hand corner when SSL is being used on a secure page.

Second, many areas of our registration websites require the use of a registrant user ID and password as an additional security measure to protect against unauthorized access to account information.

_How We Use The Information We Collect From Our Registration Customers:_

We use personal information collected during the execution of our services for a variety of purposes. In particular, we may collect your name, physical address, email address, phone number and payment specifics to: 

  * fulfill the transactions you initiate
  * provide notices about the status of your account
  * better understand how our web site and its various features are being used
  * conduct market research 
  * present you with customized and relevant information and offers on behalf of your show organizer
  * allow you to participate in surveys, access and download data, and use other interactive features of our services
  * carry out functions we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (e) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (f) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain

_Registrant Opt-Out Choices_ **:**

We do not send email messages to our registrants that are not authorized by the event organizer. If specified by the event organizer, we provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email communication from us.

_Cookies:_

CompuSystems uses cookies only for session-state management and has no plan to use cookies for any other purpose. We will revise this policy if we elect to use cookie technology for any other purpose.

**Lead Retrieval Customers**

We have taken a number of steps to assure the protection of personal or confidential information sent to or from us.

First, as it pertains to online transactions, we require that a secure session be established. This is done any time customers supply or access personal or confidential information in one of our online areas. This technology creates a private conversation that only the communicating computers understand, ensuring that the transmitted information remains confidential. Furthermore, when customers access pages requesting or presenting financial or personal data, we utilize 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to prevent others from accessing it while in transit. Most browsers display a padlock icon in the bottom right-hand corner when SSL is being used on a secure page.

Second, our online ordering website requires the use of a user ID and password as an additional security measure to protect against unauthorized access to account information.

Third, in order to bring our customers certain services offered through our websites, we work with trusted non-affiliated companies. If we have to share any personal information with these companies in order to provide a product or service, we take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure these companies protect this information, which may include requiring they complete questionnaires and/or take other evaluative measures of their information and security systems, safeguards, and practices prior to selection as a business partner. These measures may also include implementing contractual provisions to ensure the security and confidentiality of  customer information. In some cases, we may also audit these companies to verify the continued security of their systems and practices.

_How We Use The Information We Collect From Our Lead Retrieval Customers:_

We use personal information collected during the execution of our services for a variety of purposes. In particular, we may collect your name, physical address, email address, phone number and payment specifics to: 

  * fulfill the transactions you initiate
  * provide notices about the status of your account
  * better understand how our web site and its various features are being used
  * conduct market research 
  * present you with customized and relevant information and offers
  * allow you to participate in surveys, access and download data, and use other interactive features of our services
  * notify you about changes to our services, any products or services we offer or provide through our services, our terms and conditions applicable to our services, or this Privacy Policy
  * carry out functions we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (e) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (f) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain

_Customer Opt-Out Choices_ **:**

We provide customers with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email communication from us. 

_Cookies:_

CompuSystems uses cookies only for session-state management and has no plan to use cookies for any other purpose. We will revise this policy if we elect to use cookie technology for any other purpose. 

## 

### **CANADA’S ANTI-SPAM LAW (CASL)**

 **Opt-in to Email and Text Communication**

To ensure compliance with unsolicited commercial email and text laws, show organizers must obtain explicit “opt-in” consent from all exhibitors which specifically permits CompuSystems, as an official show contractor, to contact exhibitors by email or text to promote our services that are specific to the organizer’s event. 

If CompuSystems is required to send email marketing solicitations to registrants on behalf of the event organizer, event organizer must obtain explicit “opt-in” consent unless the following criteria are met:

  * They are sending responses to a current customer, or someone who has inquired in the last six months.
  * They are sending messages that provide information about a purchase, subscription, membership, account, loan, or other ongoing relationship, including delivery of product updates or upgrades.
  * They are sending messages that provide warranty, recall, safety, or security information about a product or service purchased by the recipient.

Furthermore, show organizers may not use rented, traded, or purchased lists, email append lists, or any list that contains email addresses/phone numbers captured in any other method than by express consent. 

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy or privacy practices, please contact us at privacyofficer@csireg.com
